{
  "language": [
    {
      "language": "spanish",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Fill in the blank: My coat is old. Mi ____ está viejo.",
      "answers": ["abriga", "bluso", "abrigas", "faldo"],
      "index": 2
    },
    {
      "language": "spanish",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Fill in the blank: The blouse is green. La ____ es verde.",
      "answers": ["camo", "abriga", "seda", "blusa"],
      "index": 3
    },
    {
      "language": "spanish",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Fill in the blank: Those pants are dirty. Esos pantalones están ____.",
      "answers": ["suicos", "suicas", "limpios", "vierda"],
      "index": 1
    },
    {
      "language": "spanish",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Fill in the blank: I am happy. Yo estoy ___.",
      "answers": ["contente", "contenta", "contento", "contenti"],
      "index": 2
    },
    {
      "language": "spanish",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Fill in the blank: The teacher is happy. El maestro está ___",
      "answers": ["enojada", "enojados", "enojado", "enojadi"],
      "index": 2
    },
    {
      "language": "spanish",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Fill in the blank: My brother is angry. Mi hermano está ___",
      "answers": ["contente", "contenta", "contento", "contenti"],
      "index": 2
    },
    {
      "language": "spanish",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Fill in the blank: Are there carrots in the soup?. ¿Hay ____s en la sopa?",
      "answers": ["zanahoria", "zanahora", "carrothoria", "manzana"],
      "index": 0
    },
    {
      "language": "spanish",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Fill in the blank: Are there toasts for breakfast?. ¿Hay ___ para desayunar?",
      "answers": ["enchilados", "enchiladas", "tostadas", "toastas"],
      "index": 2
    },
    {
      "language": "spanish",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Fill in the blank: You ask for milk. Tú pides ___.",
      "answers": ["lecho", "lecha", "leche", "milko"],
      "index": 2
    },
    {
      "language": "spanish",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Fill in the blank: You ask for lunch. Tú pides el ___.",
      "answers": ["almuerzo", "cena", "almuerza", "aperitivo"],
      "index": 0
    },
    {
      "language": "french",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Choose the correct translation: Je ne regarde pas très souvent de film.",
      "answers": [
        "Why are you crying?",
        "Why are you wearing a jacket?",
        "I don't watch movies very often.",
        "What is the conventional way of doing this."
      ],
      "index": 2
    },
    {
      "language": "french",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Translate boat in french",
      "answers": ["Bateau", "Baton", "Bar", "Blaireau"],
      "index": 0
    },
    {
      "language": "french",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "What is the imperative, singular form of aller?",
      "answers": ["Vas", "Vont", "Va", "Allez"],
      "index": 2
    }
  ]
}
